<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Writing | My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://aubreyrhodes.github.com/blog/categories/writing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aubreyrhodes.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-07-09T22:07:06-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://aubreyrhodes.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aubrey Rhodes]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goals]]></title>
    <link href="http://aubreyrhodes.github.com/blog/2012/07/01/goals/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-01T19:49:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://aubreyrhodes.github.com/blog/2012/07/01/goals</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So, today we enter the second half of 2012 and I figured it was a good time to review my progress on some goals I had set out for myself and add one more.</p>

<p><img src="https://img.skitch.com/20120702-jngidbeg39ckq8y4cbk32kqs8n.png" style="margin: 15px;" alt="2012 Goals"/></p>

<p>In January, I set out 4 goals for myself and posted them to Facebook so that I would have some kind of accountability. I wanted all of the goals to be easily measurable and have a big impact on my life. As of the end of June I've made some really good progress so far:</p>

<ul>
<li>I've bought my new house and it's opened up a whole new neighborhood of Atlanta to me.</li>
<li>Thanks to my <a href="http://highgroove.com">employer</a> providing a personal trainer and starting to train for the Peachtree Roadrace, I've been working out 4 times a week on average and have lost 20 lbs. so far this year.</li>
<li>I've adopted a great new friend; a 3 month old border collie mix named Ernest and he's been the highlight of my summer so far.</li>
</ul>


<p>I'll admit that I haven't made much progress on my final goal of starting a business thus far, but I've got some big plans for the next six months. The year so far has been transformative, and I attribute that completely to setting big goals in January.</p>

<p>Because these goals have been a success so far, I've decided to add one more. For the month of July, I want to write at least 5 blog posts per week. I have wanted to work on my writing for some time now, and I have decided to bias towards getting content in front of people instead of waiting for inspiration to hit.</p>

<p>These will mostly relate to my professional life as a software developer and may tend to be more technical in nature. I definitely welcome any feedback or suggestions at aubrey.c.rhodes@gmail.com.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
